# **ALI PAJAND**

Montreal, Quebec/Canada • ali.pajand@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/alipajand/ @ alipajand.com/en

# Senior Frontend Developer

# Summary

I'm an extroverted, energetic, highly positive and hardworking developer with +8 years of expertises in web development (**react** and **vue**) with a history of graphics knowledge.

My main affection is to learn about web and new technologies from various sources of people. I enjoy encountering challenges for which my problem solving ability manifests and expands. I love to see beautiful codes that have an adherence to standards and open-source solutions. I try to figure out all possible solutions but then act based on best practices and standard ways.

To find out more, visit my **Linkedin** account.

# Work Experiences

Mar 2018 - Feb 2022

#### Senior Frontend Developer

#### Ctrl+Tech

- Implement websites and admin panels for: (Tarafdari, Advva, Mapeeno, Tazebar, Ctrltech, Admartiz, Banikar, Techtoman, Bidzila, FirouzehPlat,...)
- Implement PWA for some of application
- Implement attractive online chats and map segmentation based on vue and react
- Implement some custom service worker to work in offline mode
- Work with firebase messaging and other socket based services
- Design and implement email templates
- Write BDD tests for some of projects that are mentioned above

Jan 2014 - Dec 2017

#### Frontend Developer

### Rayvarz Software Engineering

- Working in BPMS team (business process management system to rewrite online admin panel and portal in vue)
- Mentoring, UI Discussion and preparing prototypes for programmers
- Collaborate on service catalogue for Ministry of Economic Affairs of Iran
- Change user interface of eOffice to create new sense and change admin panel arguments and texts
- Maintain the old eOffice services and add new feature
- Start to implement new version of company website

## Remote Experiences

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

Senior Frontend Developer (Oslo, Norway)

**BirdFlocks** 

Impletent main panel with next js framework in react as a single project

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Senior Frontend Developer (San Francisco, US)

Galliot

Implement website and its admin panel in nuxt js framework in vue

May 2020 - Dec 2020

Senior Frontend Developer (Dubai, UAE)

Jeanwest

Impletent main panel in nuxt and vue frameworks

Pure version and <u>Nuxt</u> as ssr framework <u>Vuex</u> as State management tools  Familiar with <u>Typescript</u>		Redux as State management tools Familiar with Typescript
		Pure version and <b>Next</b> as ssr framework
Vue js   Nuxt js		React js   Next js   Gatsby
		Skills
	Allame Tabataba'i University	
Sep 2010 - Aug 2014	B.Sc. Engineering/Industrial Management	
	Process	actors to ose cloud compating by oniversity students in Educational
	Allame Tabataba'i University  Thesis: Identification of Factors to Use Cloud Computing by University Students in Educational	
Sep 2014 - Aug 2018	M.Sc. Computer/Information Technology Administration	
		Education ————————————————————————————————————
	Implementing three gen	eration of website in these years
	Lahtiprecision	
Jan 2015 - Jan 2017	Frontend Developer (Lahti, Finland)	
	Help to develop and ma	intain the global application in angular
Apr 2019 - Jul 2019	Frontend Developer ( <i>Timely</i>	Vancouver, Canada)
	Deltaban / 3Click	in nuxt and vue frameworks
Jan 2020 - May 2020	Sellioi Floritella Deve	eloper (Tehran, Iran)

Notifications and Service Workers Chrome Extension

Onesignal & Google Firebase Write some extensions for chrome browser

Progressive Web Apps (PWA) Version Controller

Workbox Git, SVN and TFS

Created with 🔽 VisualCV